{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.8.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":5400,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":41,"width":970,"height":535,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"SmartShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"If the abandon code is “No Room in To Location (D)”, press the F3 key and type IPLMA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_1","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IPLMA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_1","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_1","title":"Click the white box and type IPLMA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_1","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7911","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_1","Text_Entry_Box_1","Success_Shape_1","Hint_Shape_1","Failure_Shape_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7911"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"To find the quantity of the Product (12609263), press Enter.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_4","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_4","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7969","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_3","SmartShape_4","Text_Entry_Box_4","Hint_Shape_4"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7969"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"In the physical location, verify that the quantity matches the quantity in the IPLMA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_8","title":"If the quantities match, exit. If the quantity does not match write the correct quantity in the “Additional Information” field on the Abandon Log. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_46","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_46","title":"Press the Enter key to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7992","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_5","SmartShape_6","SmartShape_8","Text_Entry_Box_46","Hint_Shape_46"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7992"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"To verify the inserts dimensions, press the F3 key and type IMPRD in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_3","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IMPRD"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_3","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_3","title":"Click the white box and type IMPRD. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_3","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8015","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_9","Text_Entry_Box_3","Success_Shape_3","Hint_Shape_3","Failure_Shape_3"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8015"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":"To look at the attributes of a Product (12609263), press Enter.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_21","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_25","title":"Recommended Insert Dimensions ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":"Current Insert Dimensions ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_6","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_6","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8085","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_12","SmartShape_15","SmartShape_20","SmartShape_21","SmartShape_25","SmartShape_26","Text_Entry_Box_6","Hint_Shape_6"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8085"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_16","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_17","title":"Compare the recommended insert dimensions to the current insert dimensions. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":"If the current insert is smaller than the recommended insert, look for an appropriate location for the parts. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_22","title":"If the current insert dimensions are correct, Exit to the Abandon Log and select the correct abandon reason. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_47","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_47","title":"Press the F3 key to  compare the current case cap in IMPRD to IIPAA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8108","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_16","SmartShape_17","SmartShape_18","SmartShape_19","SmartShape_22","Text_Entry_Box_47","Hint_Shape_47"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8108"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":"To compare the current case cap in IMPRD to IIPAA, type IIPAA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_7","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IIPAA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_4","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_7","title":"Click the white box and type IIPAA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_4","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8131","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_23","Text_Entry_Box_7","Success_Shape_4","Hint_Shape_7","Failure_Shape_4"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8131"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":"Enter the Product Number (12609263) in the “Product” field, then press Enter.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_8","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_5","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_8","title":"Click the white box and type 12609263 then press Enter.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_5","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8185","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_27","Text_Entry_Box_8","Success_Shape_5","Hint_Shape_8","Failure_Shape_5"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8185"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_108","title":"Verify that the case cap in IIPAA matches the current case cap in IMPRD. In this case, the case cap matches. If the case cap does not match, the data must be amended. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_109","title":"Note that the replenishment level shown here (-1) is a site-specific recommendation. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8208","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_30","SmartShape_108","SmartShape_109"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":240},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8208"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_31","title":"To amend data in the “Case Cap” column field, press the Tab key to navigate to the “Min Sel” column. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_32","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_10","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_10","title":"Press the Tab key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8250","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_31","SmartShape_32","Text_Entry_Box_10","Hint_Shape_10"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8250"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_33","title":"Press the Tab key to navigate to the “Rpln Lvl” column. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_34","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_11","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_11","title":"Press the Tab key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8273","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_33","SmartShape_34","Text_Entry_Box_11","Hint_Shape_11"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8273"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_35","title":"Press the Tab key to navigate to the “Case Cap” column. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_36","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_12","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_12","title":"Press the Tab key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8296","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_35","SmartShape_36","Text_Entry_Box_12","Hint_Shape_12"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8296"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_111","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_38","title":"Enter the correct amount from the IMPRD (145614561456) in the “Case Cap” column fields. Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_14","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["145614561456"]},"constraints":{"length":12}}}},{"id":"Text_Animation_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Animation_29","roles":{}},{"id":"Success_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_8","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_14","title":"Click the white box and type 145614561456 then press Enter.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_8","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8319","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_111","SmartShape_38","Text_Entry_Box_14","Success_Shape_8","Hint_Shape_14","Failure_Shape_8"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":210},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8319"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_41","title":"To get an insert with the recommended dimensions, press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_15","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_15","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8473","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_41","Text_Entry_Box_15","Hint_Shape_15"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8473"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_40","title":"Type IIAVA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_16","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IIAVA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_10","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_16","title":"Click the white box and type IIAVA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_10","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8496","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_40","Text_Entry_Box_16","Success_Shape_10","Hint_Shape_16","Failure_Shape_10"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8496"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_43","title":"Fill in the appropriate information: Category (S), From Location (N), To Location (6), Minimum Location Height (4). Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_17","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["SN64"]},"constraints":{"length":4}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_112","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Animation_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Animation_30","roles":{}},{"id":"Success_Shape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_11","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_17","title":"Click the white box and type SN64 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_11","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8558","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_43","Text_Entry_Box_17","SmartShape_112","Success_Shape_11","Hint_Shape_17","Failure_Shape_11"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":210},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8558"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_44","title":"To browse the available locations, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_18","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_18","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8684","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_44","Text_Entry_Box_18","Hint_Shape_18"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8684"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_20","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_100","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_106","title":"Using the arrow keys, navigate to the appropriate location and make a note of the location (N64141A1). ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_20","title":"Press the Down Arrow key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8707","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_20","SmartShape_100","SmartShape_106","Hint_Shape_20"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8707"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_47","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_21","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_107","title":"Press and hold Ctrl and C to exit the “LOCATION BROWSE DETAIL” screen. Make a note of the location details (N64141A1). ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_21","title":"Press and hold the Ctrl and C keys. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8833","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_47","Text_Entry_Box_21","SmartShape_107","Hint_Shape_21"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8833"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_48","title":"To assign a new location to the part, press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_22","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_22","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8856","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_48","Text_Entry_Box_22","Hint_Shape_22"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8856"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_51","title":"Enter IIPAA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_23","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IIPAA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_13","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_23","title":"Click the white box and type IIPAA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_13","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8879","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_51","Text_Entry_Box_23","Success_Shape_13","Hint_Shape_23","Failure_Shape_13"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8879"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_52","title":"Enter the Product Number (12609263) in the “Product” field, then press Enter.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_24","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_14","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_24","title":"Click the white box and type 12609263 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_14","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8902","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_52","Text_Entry_Box_24","Success_Shape_14","Hint_Shape_24","Failure_Shape_14"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8902"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_54","title":"Press the Tab key to navigate to the “Add” section and press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_55","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_26","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_26","title":"Press the Tab key and then the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8925","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_54","SmartShape_55","Text_Entry_Box_26","Hint_Shape_26"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8925"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_56","title":"Type the new location (N64141A1) in the Location column field. Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_27","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["N64141A1"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_16","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_27","title":"Click the white box and type N64141A1 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_16","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9063","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_56","Text_Entry_Box_27","Success_Shape_16","Hint_Shape_27","Failure_Shape_16"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9063"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_58","title":"To accept the new location and the data in the “PRODUCT LOCATION ASSIGNMENTS” screen, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_28","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_28","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9145","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_58","Text_Entry_Box_28","Hint_Shape_28"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9145"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_59","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_59","title":"To move the Material to the new bin location, press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_29","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_29","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9168","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_59","Text_Entry_Box_29","Hint_Shape_29"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9168"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_61","title":"To move the Material to the new bin location, enter ISPMH in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_30","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["ISPMH"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_17","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_30","title":"Click the white box and type ISPMH. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_17","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9191","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_61","Text_Entry_Box_30","Success_Shape_17","Hint_Shape_30","Failure_Shape_17"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9191"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_31","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["701565294"]},"constraints":{"length":9}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_102","title":"Enter the License Plate number (701565294) in the “LP” field, then press the Tab key to the “From Loc” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_18","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_31","title":"Click the white box and type 701565294 then press Tab. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_18","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9253","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_31","SmartShape_102","Success_Shape_18","Hint_Shape_31","Failure_Shape_18"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9253"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_67","title":"Press the Tab key to the “To Loc” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_70","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_70","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_33","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_33","title":"Press the Tab key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9355","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_67","SmartShape_70","Text_Entry_Box_33","Hint_Shape_33"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9355"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_71","title":"Enter the Main Bin location (N64141A1) and press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_34","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["N64141A1"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_20","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_34","title":"Click the white box and type N64141A1 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_20","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12319","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_71","Text_Entry_Box_34","Success_Shape_20","Hint_Shape_34","Failure_Shape_20"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12319"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_75","title":"To choose the highlighted license plate and its quantity, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_35","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_35","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9441","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_75","Text_Entry_Box_35","Hint_Shape_35"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9441"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_76","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_76","title":"Enter the quantity to move (399), then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_36","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["399"]},"constraints":{"length":3}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_21","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_36","title":"Click the white box and type 399 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_21","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9464","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_76","Text_Entry_Box_36","Success_Shape_21","Hint_Shape_36","Failure_Shape_21"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9464"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_79","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_79","title":"Press Enter to assign the inventory to the new location. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_37","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_37","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9487","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_79","Text_Entry_Box_37","Hint_Shape_37"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9487"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_80","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_80","title":"Press N for “No” in response to the “Create RF work?” message. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_38","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["N"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_22","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_38","title":"Click the white box and type N. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_22","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9510","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_80","Text_Entry_Box_38","Success_Shape_22","Hint_Shape_38","Failure_Shape_22"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9510"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_85","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_85","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_40","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_101","title":"The system will automatically generate the next license plate that can be moved. To exit the “Pallet Moving” screen, press and hold the Ctrl and C keys. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_40","title":"Press and hold the Ctrl and C keys. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9556","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_85","Text_Entry_Box_40","SmartShape_101","Hint_Shape_40"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9556"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_41","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_104","title":"Press the Esc key to exit the screen and return to the “DALLAS SYSTEM MENUS” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_41","title":"Press the Esc key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9579","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_41","SmartShape_104","Hint_Shape_41"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9579"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_88","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_88","title":"Press the F3 key to open the “NAVIGATOR” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_42","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_42","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9622","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_88","Text_Entry_Box_42","Hint_Shape_42"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9622"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_89","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_89","title":"To complete the abandon and the Pallet Move, type RMVUC in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_44","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["RMVUC"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_24","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_44","title":"Click the white box and type RMVUC. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_24","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9645","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_89","Text_Entry_Box_44","Success_Shape_24","Hint_Shape_44","Failure_Shape_24"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9645"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_45","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["701565294"]},"constraints":{"length":9}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_105","title":"Enter the license plate information (701565294), in the “License Plate” field. Then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_25","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_45","title":"Click the white box and type 701565294 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_25","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9703","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_45","SmartShape_105","Success_Shape_25","Hint_Shape_45","Failure_Shape_25"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9703"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_110","title":"Complete the PU work unit. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20887","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_110"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":210},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20887"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_94","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_94","title":"You have completed this process. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10036","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_94"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":210},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10036"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"NoRoomInToLocationTraining","class":"project","title":"NoRoomInToLocationTraining","children":["Slide7911","Slide7969","Slide7992","Slide8015","Slide8085","Slide8108","Slide8131","Slide8185","Slide8208","Slide8250","Slide8273","Slide8296","Slide8319","Slide8473","Slide8496","Slide8558","Slide8684","Slide8707","Slide8833","Slide8856","Slide8879","Slide8902","Slide8925","Slide9063","Slide9145","Slide9168","Slide9191","Slide9253","Slide9355","Slide12319","Slide9441","Slide9464","Slide9487","Slide9510","Slide9556","Slide9579","Slide9622","Slide9645","Slide9703","Slide20887","Slide10036"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":[],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide7911","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide7969","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide7992","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide8015","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide8085","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide8108","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide8131","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide8185","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide8208","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide8250","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide8273","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide8296","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide8319","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide8473","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide8496","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide8558","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide8684","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide8707","title":"Slide 18"},{"id":"Slide8833","title":"Slide 19"},{"id":"Slide8856","title":"Slide 20"},{"id":"Slide8879","title":"Slide 21"},{"id":"Slide8902","title":"Slide 22"},{"id":"Slide8925","title":"Slide 23"},{"id":"Slide9063","title":"Slide 24"},{"id":"Slide9145","title":"Slide 25"},{"id":"Slide9168","title":"Slide 26"},{"id":"Slide9191","title":"Slide 27"},{"id":"Slide9253","title":"Slide 28"},{"id":"Slide9355","title":"Slide 29"},{"id":"Slide12319","title":"Slide 30"},{"id":"Slide9441","title":"Slide 31"},{"id":"Slide9464","title":"Slide 32"},{"id":"Slide9487","title":"Slide 33"},{"id":"Slide9510","title":"Slide 34"},{"id":"Slide9556","title":"Slide 35"},{"id":"Slide9579","title":"Slide 36"},{"id":"Slide9622","title":"Slide 37"},{"id":"Slide9645","title":"Slide 38"},{"id":"Slide9703","title":"Slide 39"},{"id":"Slide20887","title":"Slide 40"},{"id":"Slide10036","title":"Slide 41"}]}